A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) grant and fellowship declinations and withdrawals, 1968-1996; 4; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 document boxes: 9 letter size boxes
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Semmler, Willi (Box 61, Folder 903)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Masterson, Daniel (Box 61, Folder 904)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Nakagawa, Masko (Box 61, Folder 905)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Nelson, John (Box 61, Folder 906)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Rapp, William (Box 61, Folder 907)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Simon, Thomas (Box 61, Folder 908)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Yonally, Dawn (Box 61, Folder 909)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Amari, Hiroshi (Box 61, Folder 910)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Code, Patrick (Box 61, Folder 911)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Dabney, Dyron Keith (Box 61, Folder 912)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Gordon, David B. (Box 61, Folder 913)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Gu, Linyu (Box 61, Folder 914)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Guelcher, Gregory (Box 61, Folder 915)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Hatch, Walter (Box 61, Folder 916)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Helfrich, Kurt (Box 61, Folder 917)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Hiener, Terry (Box 61, Folder 918)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Hirayma, Hina (Box 62, Folder 919)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Johnson, Brett (Box 62, Folder 920)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Kashiwazaki, Chikako (Box 62, Folder 921)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Knight, Gary Alan (Box 62, Folder 922)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Koikari, Mire, 1993-1996 (Box 62, Folder 923)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Lyon, Beth (Box 62, Folder 924)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Matsuoka, Hideaki (Box 62, Folder 925)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - McKelway, Matthew (Box 62, Folder 926)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Meli, Mark Frederick (Box 62, Folder 927)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Meyerson, Christopher (Box 62, Folder 928)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Park, Cheol Hee (Box 62, Folder 929)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Platt, Brian Wesley (Box 62, Folder 930)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Rath, Eric (Box 62, Folder 931)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Ruoff, Kenneth (Box 62, Folder 932)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Schneider, Justin (Box 62, Folder 933)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Shibusawa, Naoko (Box 62, Folder 934)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Shoskes, Ellen (Box 62, Folder 935)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Slaymaker, Douglas (Box 62, Folder 936)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Smith, Christienne (Box 62, Folder 937)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Smith, William Donald (Box 62, Folder 938)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Sono, Reiko (Box 62, Folder 939)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Solis, Mireya (Box 62, Folder 940)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Stocker, Joel Floyd (Box 63, Folder 941)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Sugimoto, Michael (Box 63, Folder 942)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Suzuki, Akira (Box 63, Folder 943)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Walker, Brett (Box 63, Folder 944)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - White, Linda (Box 63, Folder 945)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Yamamoto, Mayumi (Box 63, Folder 946)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Hannashiro, Roy (Box 63, Folder 947)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Igarashi, Yoshikuni (Box 63, Folder 948)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Inoue, Kyoko (Box 63, Folder 949)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Kanagy, Ruth (Box 63, Folder 950)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Lebra, Takie S. (Box 63, Folder 951)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Maga, Timothy (Box 63, Folder 952)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Matsusaka, Yoshihisa (Box 63, Folder 953)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Metraux, Daniel (Box 63, Folder 954)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Patterson, Dennis (Box 63, Folder 955)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Peng, Dajin (Box 63, Folder 956)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Phillips, Quitman (Box 63, Folder 957)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Pauka, Kirstin (Box 63, Folder 958)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Raynal, Jean-Marc (Box 63, Folder 959)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Robinson, Patricia (Box 63, Folder 960)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Sedgwick, Mitchell (Box 63, Folder 961)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Smith, Kerry (Box 63, Folder 962)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Sorensen, David, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 963)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Szatrowski, Polly (Box 64, Folder 964)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Usui, Chikako (Box 64, Folder 965)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Weston, Victoria (Box 64, Folder 966)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Ashbaugh, William (Box 64, Folder 967)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Bernstein, Andrew (Box 64, Folder 968)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Fujihira, Shinju (Box 64, Folder 969)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Guelcher, Gregory (Box 64, Folder 970)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Jenike, Brenda (Box 64, Folder 971)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Johnson, Brett (Box 64, Folder 972)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Kawabata, Eiji (Box 64, Folder 973)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Kishigami, Naoko (Box 64, Folder 974)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Keaveney, Christopher (Box 64, Folder 975)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Kyu Hyun (Box 64, Folder 976)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Lane, David (Box 64, Folder 977)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Lee, Soyoung (Box 64, Folder 978)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Lockyer, Angus (Box 64, Folder 979)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Martin, Sherry (Box 64, Folder 980)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Matsuoka, Hideaki (Box 64, Folder 981)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Milhaupt, Terry (Box 64, Folder 982)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Ruoff, Kenneth (Box 64, Folder 983)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Subramanian, Mukund (Box 64, Folder 984)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Wallner, Klaus (Box 64, Folder 985)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Welch, Patricia (Box 64, Folder 986)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Witteveen, Guven (Box 64, Folder 987)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Workshop 1995-1996 declinations - Zeng, Kangmin (Box 64, Folder 988)
- Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) grant and fellowship awardees, 1985-1996; 5; 1.04 Cubic Feet 2.5 document boxes: 1 legal size box and 1.5 letter boxes
  Files in the subseries document awardees of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Joint Committee on Korean Studies' (JCJS) different grant and fellowship programs. As the contents of the subseries demonstrates, the subseries does not hold the files for all awardees of these programs. The award years documented within the subseries chiefly span from the mid-1980s through the early 1990s. The grant and fellowship programs the JCKS administered which the subseries documents include:
  - Dissertation Fellowship for pre-doctoral researchers - Advanced Research Grant for post-doctoral researchers - Research Planning Grant - Korea Foundation doctoral fellowship
  Awardees documented within the subseries researched such subject areas as economics, economic development, history, literature, culture, religion, politics, sociology, and anthropology in relation to Korea (particularly South Korea/Republic of Korea (ROK)).
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 awardees - Kim, Jim Yong, 1985-1989 (Box 65, Folder 989)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 awardees - Cho, Hein, 1986-1988 (Box 65, Folder 990)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 awardees - Allen, J. Michael, 1986-1989 (Box 65, Folder 991)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 awardees - Stevenson, Miwha, 1986-1990 (Box 65, Folder 992)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Burmeister, Larry L., 1986-1988 (Box 65, Folder 993)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Buswell, Robert E., 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 994)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Provine, Robert C., 1986-1988 (Box 65, Folder 995)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Gereffi, Gary A., 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 996)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Palais, James B., 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 997)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Kwon, Hack Soo, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 998)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Han, Gyoung-hae, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 999)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Hewings, Geoffrey, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 1000)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Kim, Kumja, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 1001)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Janelli, Roger, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 1002)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Park, Chai Bin, 1987-1990 (Box 65, Folder 1003)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1989-1990 awardees - Wells, Ken, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 1004)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1989-1990 awardees - Park, Sung-bae and Buswell, Robert, 1988-1995 (Box 66, Folder 1005)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1989-1990 awardees - Lee, Peter, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 1006)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1990-1991 awardees - Lett, Denise, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1007)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1990-1991 awardees - Burgess, Lewis, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1008)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1990-1991 awardees - Lee, Timothy S., 1990-1995 (Box 66, Folder 1009)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1990-1991 awardees - Cheng, Tun-Jen, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 1010)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1990-1991 awardees - Fulton, Bruce (Box 66, Folder 1011)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1990-1991 awardees - Haboush, JaHyun Kim, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 1012)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1991-1992 awardees - Rogers, Ronald, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1013)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1991-1992 awardees - Seel, John B., 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1014)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1991-1992 awardees - So, Carolyn, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1015)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1991-1992 awardees - Schmid, Andre (Box 66, Folder 1016)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1991-1992 awardees - Best, Jonathan, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 1017)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1991-1992 awardees - Pai, Hyung-Il, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 1018)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1991-1992 awardees - Park, Soon Wan (Box 66, Folder 1019)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1991-1992 awardees - Shultz, Edward (Box 66, Folder 1020)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Kang, David, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1021)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Kang, Kenneth, 1991-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1022)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Lee, Yung Chul, 1991-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1023)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Lee, Namhee, 1991-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1024)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Kim, Hyun Mee, 1991-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1025)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1992-1993 awardees - Kim, Jong Myung, 1991-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1026)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1992-1993 awardees - McCann, David, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1027)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1992-1993 awardees - Barnes, Gina, 1992-1995 (Box 67, Folder 1028)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1992-1993 awardees - King, J. Ross P., 1991-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1029)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Korea Foundation doctoral fellowship 1992 awardees - Kim, Dongno (Box 67, Folder 1030)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Korea Foundation doctoral fellowship 1992 awardees - Huang, Chang-Ling, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1031)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1995-1996 awardee - Pai, Hyung II (Box 71, Folder 1133)
- Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) grant and fellowship declinations and withdrawals, 1983-1996; 6; 1.8 Cubic Feet 4.5 document boxes: 1 legal size box and 3.5 letter size boxes
  Files in this subseries document applicants to the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Joint Committee on Korean Studies' (JCKS) different grant and fellowship programs who did not get an award. Most of the applicants were declined acceptance by the JCKS, some were initially designated as alternates but were then declined, and some were awarded a grant or fellowship but then withdrew, mostly because they received grant support from other sources. As the contents of the subseries demonstrates, the subseries does not hold the files for all declinations of these programs. The award years documented within the subseries originate from a time span between the mid-1980s and 1990 and then from 1995 to 1996 when the JCKS ended. The grant and fellowship programs the JCKS administered which the subseries documents include:
  - Dissertation Fellowship for pre-doctoral researchers
  Files include the applicant's research proposal and accompanying application materials as well as the declination letter from the JCKS. Some files include other documents like additional correspondence.
  Applicants documented within the subseries researched such subject areas as economics, economic development, international trade, labor, politics, sociology, child development, gender, women, culture, music, literature, linguistics, religion, history, and education in relation to Korea (particularly South Korea/Republic of Korea (ROK)).
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Kwon, Yung-Hee, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1032)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Lee, Jisoon, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1033)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - McArthur, Leslie, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1034)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Park, Kyung, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1035)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Park, Mikyung, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1036)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - No, Kyu (Box 67, Folder 1037)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Kim, Yong Choon, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1038)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Kim, Elaine Haikyung, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 1039)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Kim, Uichol, 1983-1986 (Box 67, Folder 1040)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Lee, Mikyung, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 1041)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Jang, Mu Seok, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1042)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Kim, Seung-kyung, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1043)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Hong, Hanhee, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1044)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Bernen, Rebecca M., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1045)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Jeong, Changik, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1046)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Ahn, Jeong Khn, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1047)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Ha, Yong Chool, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1048)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Horan, Barbara, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1049)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Lee, Chung-Myun and Kontuly, Thomas, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1050)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Choi, Soonja, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1051)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Gerdts, Donna, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1052)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Kwon, Jene K., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1053)